Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1975-1990; 1
  - General, 1975-1990; 1
    - 1975-1986, 1
      - Hutto, A.L., 1975-1986 (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - Huwe, Pete, 1975-1986 (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - Huxel, George H., 1975-1986 (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - Ikard, Carol, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Ingram, Dick G., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Irion, J.D., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Isaacs, Joyce, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Isbell, Johnny, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Isenberg, Joe, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Isip, Amando, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Ivy, David M., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Ivy, Marvin, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Jackson, Abner, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Jackson, Billy, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Jackson, Charles Austin, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Jackson, Gary D., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Jackson, Henry, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Jackson, Larry, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Jackson, Lee F., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Jackson, Richard E. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Jackson, Ron, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Jackson, William C. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Jaco, Charlie, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Jacob, Gladys, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Jaffe, Morris D. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Jamar, William W., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - James, Allan, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - James, Andy M., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - James, Bonnie, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - James, Jesse, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - James, John A. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - James, Mary Anne, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - James, W. Ervin, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Janssen, Margaret, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Jarnigan, J. Leo, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Jarvis, O.C., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Jasper, Norman, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Jenkins, Robert A., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Jennings, Meredith S., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Jensen, Howard, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Jester, David L., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Jimenez, Raul Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Jobe, Clark, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Johnson, Doris J., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - Johnson, Eddie Bernice, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - Johnson, Edward O., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - Johnson, Harley A., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 44)
      - Johnson, J. Thomas, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 45)
      - Johnson, Jay, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 46)
      - Johnson, Karen R., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 47)
      - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Johnson, Milam S. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 49)
      - Johnson, Orrin W., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - Johnson, Pearce, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - Johnson, Robert E. Sr. “Bob”, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 52)
      - Johnson, Ruben H., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 53)
      - Johnson, Samuel R., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - Johnson, Thomas J., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 55)
      - Johnston, Marlin, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 56)
      - Jones, Arves E. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 57)
      - Jones, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 58)
      - Jones, Chester, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 59)
      - Jones, Eddie, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 60)
      - Jones, Frank T., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 61)
      - Jones, Gene, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 62)
      - Jones, Grant (1 of 2), 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 63)
      - Jones, Grant (2 of 2), 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 64)
      - Jones, James H., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 65)
      - Jones, Jimmie Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 66)
      - Jones, Jerome, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 67)
      - Jones, Jo Ann, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 68)
      - Jones, Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 69)
      - Jones, Lewis A., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 70)
      - Jones, Luther, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 71)
      - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. Max L., 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 72)
      - Jones, Neal T. “Buddy”, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 73)
      - Jones, Ova, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 74)
      - Jones, Philip, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 75)
      - Jones, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 76)
      - Jones, Rosemary, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 77)
      - Jones, Roy, 1975-1986 (Box 31, Folder 78)
      - Jordan, Barbara, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Jordan, George R., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Jordan, Ken, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Jordan, Larry, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Jordan, Millie R., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Jordan, Robert B., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Joseph, Frank, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Joseph, Johnny, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Joseph, Phillip, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Judin, Carl H. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Julian, Terry, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Julien, Gail, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Junell, Dan, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Junell, Frank, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Jungmichel, Charlie, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Justice, Jason, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Justice, William Wayne, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Kacir, George E., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Kampelman, Max M., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Karnes, Donna, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Kaster, James J., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Katz, Steve, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Kauffman, Albert H., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Kauhl, Anna Ruth, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Kaye, Norman L., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Kazen, E. James, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Kearney, Edward J., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Kearney, Mike J., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Keel, John M., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Keel, Thomas, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Keese, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Keeton, E.L., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Kelleher, Herbert K., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Keller, Ray, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Keller, Scott, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Kellett, Ronald Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Kelley, Carroll, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Kelley, Rusty, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Kelley, Rusty, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Kelley, Sam, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - Kelly, Brian, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - Kelly, Dee J., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - Kelly, George, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Kelly, Lou, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - Kelly, Robert I., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - Kelly, Roy E., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 46)
      - Kelsoe, Jerry, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - Kemp, Hill, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 48)
      - Kemper, Conley C., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 49)
      - Kennard, Betsy Dehoney, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - Kennard, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 51)
      - Kennedy, J. Lloyd, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - Kennedy, J.P., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 53)
      - Kennedy, Vann M., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 54)
      - Kern, William, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 55)
      - Kerr, Donald J., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 56)
      - Kersey, Clinton “Padre”, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 57)
      - Kershman, Dick, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 58)
      - Kerstein, A.E., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 59)
      - Kessel, Milton, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 60)
      - Kessler, Ronald W., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 61)
      - Ketelsen, James L., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 62)
      - Ketner, Billie, 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 63)
      - Key, Earl A., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 64)
      - Keyser, Ed L., 1975-1986 (Box 32, Folder 65)
      - Khoury, Rollin, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Kidwell, Keith R., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Kight, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Kilpatrick, Charles O., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Kim, In Kon, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Kimberlin, Sam O. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Kimbro, Marvin, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Kinch, Sam E. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - King, Edwin E., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - King, Fred, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - King, Harvey B., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - King, John Q. Taylor, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - King, Larry L., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - King, Thomas S., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Kingsbery, Lucille, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Kingston, Mike, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Kirby, William N., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Kirk, Paul G. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Kirkham, Charles D. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Kirklin, W.G., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Kisor, Keith, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Klager, James E., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Klein, Eddie A., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Klevenhagen, Johnny, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Knaggs, Fred, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Knaggs, John R., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Knape, Roslyn, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Knauss, Robert L., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Knight, Mrs. James W. “Jimmy”, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Knowlton, Danny, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - Kocurek, Willie I., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - Koliba, Homer L. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - Korioth, Al, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Korioth, Tony, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 34)
      - Korn, Angela, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 35)
      - Kothmann, Glenn H., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 36)
      - Kothmann, William D., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 37)
      - Kralj, Nicholas K., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 38)
      - Krause Publications, Inc., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 39)
      - Kreft, A. John, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 40)
      - Krier, Cynthia Taylor “Cyndi”, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - Kringel, Henry E., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 42)
      - Krischke, Pat, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 43)
      - Kritser, Tom Moylan, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 44)
      - Kronzer, W. James, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 45)
      - Krueger, Doyle E., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 46)
      - Krueger, Gilmore, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 47)
      - Krueger, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 48)
      - Krueger, Wesley, 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 49)
      - Kruse, Mr. & Mrs. John E., 1975-1986 (Box 33, Folder 50)
      - Kubecka, Warren, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Kubiak, Dan, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Kubiak, L.B., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Kuempel, Edmund, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Kuper, C.J., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Kuperman, David I., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Kyle, G.W., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Kyle, Jack D., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Kyse, Russell C., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Lack, David, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Ladd, Charles F.C., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Ladda, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Lalor, J. Lance, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Lama, Tony Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Lama, Louis, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - LaMarche, Gara, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Lambert, Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - Lampo, Johnny S., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Lancaster, Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Landgrede, James L., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Landrum, Faulk, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Lane, E.D., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Lane, Joe & Sue, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Lane, Robert B., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Laney, James E. “Pete”, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Laney, Parke, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Lanford, B.W., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Langdon, Mrs. Jim, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Langdon, Jim C., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Lange, Blanche S., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Lange, Frederick M., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Langer, Ralph, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Langford, James M., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Lanier, Chris, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Lanier, Robert C., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Lankford, Burrell, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Lapiado, Greg, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - Lashbrook, Michael J., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Laswell, Ellen, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Lasiter, R.J., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Latham, James M., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - Latham, Richard D., 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Latimer, Truett, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Latta, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Lau, Bernard & Catherine, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Lauhoff, Herman, 1975-1986 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Lava, Joan, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Laves, Bernard, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Law, C.R. “Roy”, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Lawlis, Monte D., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Lawrence, Charles B., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Lawrence, Charles E., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Lawrence, F. Lee, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Lawrence, William D. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Leach, Harold A., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - League, Thomas, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Lebermann, Lowell H., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Ledbetter, Harry & Linda, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Lee, Clarence A., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Lee, D. Henry, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Lee, Don, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Lee, Ed, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Lee, El Franco, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Lee, Eloise B., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Lee, Jack Phillip, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Lee, John R., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Lee, Maxine, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Lee, Nelda S., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Lee, Pamela, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Lee, Robert E., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Leedom, John N. (1 of 2), 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Leedom, John N. (2 of 2), 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Leem, Harry E., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Leggett, James V. Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Leggett, Sharon, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Legislature-64th, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Lehman, Dan, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Leies, John A., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Leland, Mickey, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Lemens, Vernon Sr., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Lemons, Abe, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Leonard, George W., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Leonard, Vesta, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Lester, George, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - Letsos, Eugene, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      - Levy, Sister Gertrude, 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 40)
      - Levy, Michael R., 1975-1986 (Box 35, Folder 41)
      - Lewallen, R.J. “Red”, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Lewis, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Lewis, Charles E., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Lewis, Charles R., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Lewis, Earl M., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Lewis, Gibson D. “Gib” (1 of 5), 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Lewis, Gibson D. “Gib” (2 of 5), 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Lewis, Gibson D. “Gib” (3 of 5), 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Lewis, Gibson D. “Gib” (4 of 5), 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Lewis, Gibson D. “Gib” (5 of 5), 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Lewis, Harry D., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Lewis, Jack O., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Lewis, Linda Jane, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Lewis, Maxena, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Lewis, Neeley, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Lewis, Ron E., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Lewis, Scharlene, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Ligarde, Honore, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Light, Beryl, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Lightfoot, William L., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Lightner, Candy, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Ligon, Bill, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Liguori, James A., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Lilly, Bob A., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Lilly, James L., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Linam, R.H., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Lindeman, Harvie D., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Lindley, Stephen A., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Lindsay, Jon, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Ling, Michael F., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Lingelbach, Tom, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Lipshy, Ben A., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Lipshy, Bruce A., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Lisnow, Harmon, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Little, Walden R. “Red”, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Liveley, Charles, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Liveley, Edwin L., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - Liveley, Lynne, 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Livingston, Ollie B., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - Livingston, William S., 1975-1986 (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - Lloyd, Jerry Randol, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Lock, Ben & Robin, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Lock, Ottis E., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Locke, Tom R., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Lockett, John A., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Lockhart, Earl, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Lockstedt, Barbara, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Loeb, Herman, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Loeffler, Tom, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Loftin, Paul, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Loftis, Harry, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Loftis, Jack, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Lomenzo, Beverly, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - London, David, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Long, C.J., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Long, Dan F., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Long, Steve, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Long, Stuart, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - The Long Trusts, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Longley, Joe K., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Longley, Susan, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Longoria, Raul L., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Looney, Ben, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Looney, Cullen R., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Looney, E.P., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Looney, Reverend Pete, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Looney, Robert L., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Lopez, Chacha, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Lopez, Oscar, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Lopez, Ray, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Lord, Phillip A., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Lorenz, Bob, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Lorenz, R. Wade, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Lott, Freeman, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Love, Ben F., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Love, Brenda, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Lovett, Jim D., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - Lowe, Ralph, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Lowe, Candy G., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - Lowry, Margaret Gary, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Lowry, Peter M., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Luce, Woodrow E. “Woody”, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - Luce, Thomas, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Lucey, Patrick J., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - Lucio, Eduardo A. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - Luna, Albert III, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 46)
      - Luna, Juan J. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Luna, Ronald E., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 48)
      - Lusk, Dwight E., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 49)
      - Lyles, Lt. Colonel & Mrs. Don, 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 50)
      - Lyon, Ted B. Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 51)
      - Lyons, E.A., 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 52)
      - Mabus, Ray, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - MacDonald, Robert J., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Mackey, Cecil, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Mackey, Oscar, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Madden, Wales Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Madeira, Harry, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Madera, Elbert M. (Jack), 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Madla, Frank, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Maes, Thomas M. II, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Magness, James D., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Maguire, Jack R., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Mahaffey, Curt, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Mahagan, Victor R., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Maresh, Franklin W., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Maher, Louis J., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Mahon, George, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Malcolm, William C., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Maldonado, Juan J., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Mallouf, Robert, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Malmborg, K.E., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Malone, Frank C., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Malone, Paul, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Maloney, Marynell, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Maloney, Robert B., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Manatt, Charles T., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Manges, Candi, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Manges, Chic, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Manges, Clinton, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Manges, Jack C., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Manges, Hondo, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Manges, Ruth, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Manges, Ruthie, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Mangum, Preston P., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Mann, Gerald E., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - Mann, James E., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Mann, Johnny S., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Mann, Kenneth, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Mann, Tom E., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Manns, Phyllis, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Manuel, Gus, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - Manuppelli, Molly, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Maples, Harold, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - Marak, Dorothy, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - Marchand, Darryl T., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - Marcus, Stanley, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - Maresh, Frank W., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 46)
      - Margetich, John G., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - Marinovic, Margie, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - Marlow, Fred G., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - Maroney, Jack D., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - Marshall, Bruce, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - Marshall, Geo. K. (George), 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - Marshall, Hulen “Hog-Jaw”, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 53)
      - Marshall, John W., 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 54)